Guide to Tuli Kupferberg and Sylvia Topp Papers MSS.385
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Cartoons/Collages, 1964, 1970-2008, undated; 20 Linear Feet in .5 record carton, 44 manuscript boxes, 1 flat folder, 3 oversize flat folders, 1 flat-file folder
  - Memory and Desire, 1985; cuid34328 (Box 137, Folder 42)
  - Miss Universe, undated; cuid34329 (Box 137, Folder 43)
  - Money Cover, 1985; cuid34330 (Box 137, Folder 44)
  - Money Talks, undated; cuid34331 (Box 137, Folder 45)
  - The More Things Derange..., 1991; cuid34332 (Box 137, Folder 46)
  - Mulroney, 1991; cuid34333 (Box 137, Folder 47)
  - Multi-Party System, undated; cuid34334 (Box 137, Folder 48)
  - Neo-Shill Media, 2004-2005; cuid34335 (Box 137, Folder 49)
  - New Body Bag, 1987; cuid34336 (Box 137, Folder 50)
  - New Frankness in Jeans, undated; cuid34337 (Box 137, Folder 51)
  - New Year, circa 1980-1989; cuid34338 (Box 137, Folder 52)
  - New York Press Cartoons, undated; cuid34339 (Box 137, Folder 53)
  - New York Great, undated; cuid34340 (Box 137, Folder 54)
  - NLCRA, undated; cuid34341 (Box 137, Folder 55)
  - No Personality, 1992; cuid34342 (Box 137, Folder 56)
  - Original Cartoons, 1985-1990; cuid34343 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Originals -- Genital Cartoons, 1990; cuid34344 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Panama -- Kinder, Gentler, 1990; cuid34345 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - PAND -- Without a Song, undated; cuid34346 (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Pardon Bush, 1992; cuid34347 (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Pawn -- Porn, 1990; cuid34348 (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Peacemaker, undated; cuid34349 (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Perot, 1992; cuid34350 (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Poor -- You Always Have Within You, undated; cuid34351 (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Prick, undated; cuid34352 (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Printed Matter, 1985; cuid34353 (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Privatize -- ACLU, 1985; cuid34354 (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Public Art, 1984; cuid34355 (Box 138, Folder 13)
  - Reagan Wouldn't Know Good Taste, 1989; cuid34356 (Box 138, Folder 14)
  - Run for Your Money, undated; cuid34357 (Box 138, Folder 15)
  - Russian Banks, 1990; cuid34358 (Box 138, Folder 16)
  - Sadat, 1981; cuid34359 (Box 138, Folder 17)
  - Second Choices, 1985; cuid34360 (Box 138, Folder 18)
  - Shit -- Pen, undated; cuid34361 (Box 138, Folder 19)
  - Single Note, undated; cuid34362 (Box 138, Folder 20)
  - Stock Exchange, 2008; cuid34363 (Box 138, Folder 21)
  - Tenement, 1988; cuid34364 (Box 138, Folder 22)
  - Thelma Blitz Colorizations, undated; cuid34365 (Box 138, Folder 23)
  - Those Who Can't; Art, undated; cuid34366 (Box 138, Folder 24)
  - Three Jokers / New Order, 1991; cuid34367 (Box 138, Folder 25)
  - Too Many Indians, undated; cuid34368 (Box 138, Folder 26)
  - Toos Pore L'Art, undated; cuid34369 (Box 138, Folder 27)
  - Trickle Down Theory, 1991; cuid34370 (Box 138, Folder 28)
  - Trotsky, 1988; cuid34371 (Box 138, Folder 29)
  - Truth Party, undated; cuid34372 (Box 138, Folder 30)
  - USA -- USSR, circa 1980-1991; cuid34373 (Box 138, Folder 31)
  - Voter, 1988; cuid34374 (Box 138, Folder 32)
  - War Carts, 1986, undated; cuid34375 (Box 138, Folder 33)
  - War -- Mixed, 1982-1985; cuid34376 (Box 138, Folder 34)
  - Wars and US History, 1984, undated; cuid34377 (Box 138, Folder 35)
  - What's at the Top?, undated; cuid34378 (Box 138, Folder 36)
  - Whitewash, circa 1983; cuid34379 (Box 138, Folder 37)
  - Who Will Pay the Economists?, 1991; cuid34380 (Box 138, Folder 38)
  - Who'll Take Care of Poopsie?, 1989; cuid34381 (Box 138, Folder 39)
  - Why am I Not Asleep?, undated; cuid34382 (Box 138, Folder 40)
  - Why Primates Laughing?, 1992; cuid34383 (Box 138, Folder 41)
  - Will Be Lazy for Food, undated; cuid34384 (Box 138, Folder 42)
  - Yeltsin for Bush, 1989; cuid34385 (Box 138, Folder 43)
  - Youth Wasted on Young, 1989; cuid34386 (Box 138, Folder 44)
  - Dentist -- Circumcision -- What Have I Got -- High School Suicides, 1997-1998; cuid34387 (Box 138, Folder 45)
  - Aids Cure -- Intensive Care -- Dying of Cancer -- American Medical, 1987-1996, undated; cuid34388 (Box 138, Folder 46)
  - New Doctor -- What Good are Kids -- Hooray for Hollywood -- Megalomycin -- Okla-Michigan Bomb, 1984-1995; cuid34389 (Box 138, Folder 47)
  - Private Prisons -- Great Moments in the History of Journalism and America, 1972-1995; cuid34390 (Box 138, Folder 48)
  - Fighter Pilot -- Stray Bullets -- Poor Babies -- How to Tie a Scarf, 1988-1990; cuid34391 (Box 138, Folder 49)
  - Miss Education -- Finding an Apartment -- Scalping Knives, 1974-2003; cuid34392 (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Great Moments in the History of the New York City / Cartoon Research Material, 1977-1978; cuid34393 (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Alberto Gonzales, undated; cuid34394 (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - Twyn Source Stuff, undated; cuid34395 (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Twyn, undated; cuid34396 (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Judges, 1987; cuid34397 (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Worm, undated; cuid34398 (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - One Foot Hung Jury, 1984; cuid34399 (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Whipped Police, 1985; cuid34400 (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - God Talks to Cops, 1989; cuid34401 (Box 139, Folder 10)
  - Bullets that Change America, undated; cuid34402 (Box 139, Folder 11)
  - Hialeah, 1982; cuid34403 (Box 139, Folder 12)
  - Scalp Em, undated; cuid34404 (Box 139, Folder 13)
  - US Leads Child Gun Fatalities, 1995-1997; cuid34405 (Box 139, Folder 14)
  - Clint-Hyp Kasovo -- Littleton, 1993-1999; cuid34406 (Box 139, Folder 15)
  - Guns Don't Kill People, undated; cuid34407 (Box 139, Folder 16)
  - Yoko, 1980-1981; cuid34408 (Box 139, Folder 17)
  - 10,000 Guns -- USA, undated; cuid34409 (Box 139, Folder 18)
  - Get Wisdom, undated; cuid34410 (Box 139, Folder 19)
  - The Bull Toils, undated; cuid34411 (Box 139, Folder 20)
  - Nuns, undated; cuid34412 (Box 139, Folder 21)
  - Grace Jones C-C #4, 1985; cuid34413 (Box 139, Folder 22)
  - Banana Republic, undated; cuid34414 (Box 139, Folder 23)
  - Iraqi Schools, 2003; cuid34415 (Box 139, Folder 24)
  - War Vendors, 2003; cuid34416 (Box 139, Folder 25)
  - Mail for FBI, 1987-2010; cuid34417 (Box 139, Folder 26)
  - Clint, 1984-1985; cuid34418 (Box 139, Folder 27)
  - Cop Shit, undated; cuid34419 (Box 139, Folder 28)
  - Lawyers, undated; cuid34420 (Box 139, Folder 29)
  - Asst. Detective (1908) via Bintel Brief, undated; cuid34421 (Box 139, Folder 30)
  - Baby Let Me Drive Your Ambulance, 2000; cuid34422 (Box 139, Folder 31)
  - Law, 1972-1999; cuid34423 (Box 139, Folder 32)
  - Gay CIA, 1983-1993; cuid34424 (Box 139, Folder 33)
  - The Plunger Lunger, undated; cuid34425 (Box 139, Folder 34)
  - Clinton -- Original / Congratulations, undated; cuid34426 (Box 139, Folder 35)
  - Piercing, undated; cuid34427 (Box 139, Folder 36)
  - Winter Far Behind, undated; cuid34428 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Young Enuf, undated; cuid34429 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - Head Start, undated; cuid34430 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - Learn in School Today, undated; cuid34431 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - Lower-Caste Indian Jobs, undated; cuid34432 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - John Reed and Harvard Review, 1992; cuid34433 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - B and W Impeach, 2004; cuid34434 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - Estrogen, undated; cuid34435 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - Will Rogers, 2007-2008; cuid34436 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - How Many are There?, undated; cuid34437 (Box 140, Folder 10)
  - US Customs, 1992; cuid34438 (Box 140, Folder 11)
  - Kick in the Balls Oxford University, undated; cuid34439 (Box 140, Folder 12)
  - Kid Like a Yuppie, undated; cuid34440 (Box 140, Folder 13)
  - Poor Babies!, 1987-1993; cuid34441 (Box 140, Folder 14)
  - Cop Shop, 1992; cuid34442 (Box 140, Folder 15)
  - I've Talked Enough Bout Myself, undated; cuid34443 (Box 140, Folder 16)
  - 106 A Corpse, undated; cuid34444 (Box 140, Folder 17)
  - Van Gogh, undated; cuid34445 (Box 140, Folder 18)
  - Seven Arts, undated; cuid34446 (Box 140, Folder 19)
  - Absolut Death and Absolute Shit Advertising, 1990; cuid34447 (Box 140, Folder 20)
  - Whitman Said, undated; cuid34448 (Box 140, Folder 21)
  - Bone Chance Gallery, undated; cuid34449 (Box 140, Folder 22)
  - Rembrandt, undated; cuid34450 (Box 140, Folder 23)
  - Door Stop, undated; cuid34451 (Box 140, Folder 24)
  - Moon Over Soho, undated; cuid34452 (Box 140, Folder 25)
  - It's Nothing, undated; cuid34453 (Box 140, Folder 26)
  - Gauguin -- School of Visual Arts, undated; cuid34454 (Box 140, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Kipnis, undated; cuid34455 (Box 140, Folder 28)
  - Artists and Government, 1981-1996; cuid34456 (Box 140, Folder 29)
  - The Children Art Union, undated; cuid34457 (Box 140, Folder 30)
  - Art Strike, undated; cuid34458 (Box 140, Folder 31)
  - Art is a Weapon, undated; cuid34459 (Box 140, Folder 32)
  - Do I Contradict Myself, undated; cuid34460 (Box 140, Folder 33)
  - Al Goldstein -- Screw, 1996, undated; cuid34461 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Playboy, 1996; cuid34462 (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Kool Kancer Concerts, 1983; cuid34463 (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Better Grade of Cancer, undated; cuid34464 (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Marx on Profit, undated; cuid34465 (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Meataholics Delight, 2000; cuid34466 (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Possible Cartoons and Collages, 1998-2001, undated; cuid34467 (Box 141, Folder 7)
  - Texass, undated; cuid34468 (Box 141, Folder 8)
  - Thatcher, 1992-2007; cuid34469 (Box 141, Folder 9)
  - Kill for Peace Again Originals, 1940-1986; cuid34470 (Box 141, Folder 10)
  - Safe Conduct Pass (Original), circa 1960s-1970s; cuid34471 (Box 141, Folder 11)
  - In Media Feces Originals, 1982-1985; cuid34472 (Box 141, Folder 12)
  - Original Drawings by Arab Kupa [Tuli Kupferberg] and Henry Gazess, 1942; cuid34473 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Cartoons and Original Drawings, undated; cuid34474 (Box 141, Folder 14-16)
  - Original Drawings -- Unsigned, undated; cuid34475 (Box 141, Folder 17-18, Box 142, Folder 1-2)
  - Beatles, Cretans, Van Gogh, 1987-1999; cuid34476 (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Fashion, Woody, Cosby, 1965-2005; cuid34477 (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Nobody for Prez, Space, Radio, 1986-2007; cuid34478 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Mao, Thatcher, Twain, 1990-2007; cuid34479 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Iraq, Remember Vietnam, 1994-2007; cuid34480 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Cartoons and Collages, 1983-2005; cuid34481 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Sports, Cable, Draft, 1984-1992; cuid34482 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Cartoons, 1985-1998; cuid34483 (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Cartoon and Collage Research Material -- Clippings, 1983-2006; cuid34484 (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Absolute Haring, 1990; cuid34485 (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Children's Art Collective -- Art is a Weapon -- Art Strike, 1980-1990; cuid34486 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Do I Contradict Myself? -- What Makes a Good Cartoon?, 1987-1988; cuid34487 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Dr. Kipnis, Last of the Rootless Cosmopolitans, Van Gogh, Art / Government, 1984-1998; cuid34488 (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - What Art Is, undated; cuid34489 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Gauguin, Blood Sculpture, 1987; cuid34490 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Grosz / Heartfield, undated; cuid34491 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Great Philosophical Questions -- Rembrandt -- Art Marketing Seminar, 1993-1996; cuid34492 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - George Segal, 1986-1993; cuid34493 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Whitman -- Seven Arts -- Van Gogh, 1990; cuid34494 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Riot Police -- Kid Like a Yuppie -- The Great Cultural War, 1985-1992; cuid34495 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Kick in the Balls, Oxford -- Lawyer -- Worms -- U.S. Customs, 1992-1996; cuid34496 (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Sting Operation -- How Many are There, 1990-1992; cuid34497 (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Darling Daughter -- Will Rogers -- Estrogen -- Impeach the President Buttons, 2008, undated; cuid34498 (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - NYPD -- John Reed / Harvard Review -- Harvard Emblem, 1984-2002; cuid34499 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Learned in School -- Preschool -- Young Enuff to Know Better, 1985-1999; cuid34500 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Piercing -- Jocelyn Elders -- Hitting, 1984-1995; cuid34501 (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Plunger Lunger -- Cop Shit -- Gay CIA -- Baby Let Me Drive Your Ambulance, 1984-2000; cuid34502 (Box 143, Folder 17)
  - Ass't Detective -- Clinton -- Mail for the FBI, 1985-1998; cuid34503 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Grace Jones -- Iraq War -- Banana Republic, 1985-2003; cuid34504 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Nuns -- The Bull Tolls -- Kosovo / Littleton, 1990-1999; cuid34505 (Box 143, Folder 20)
  - Child Gun Fatalities -- Scalp 'Em -- Haleah -- Bullets That Changed America, 1997-1999; cuid34506 (Box 143, Folder 21)
  - God Talks to A Cop -- Whipped Police -- Hung Jury -- Bribery Judge -- Worm Turned -- Judge's Salary, 1984-1989; cuid34507 (Box 143, Folder 22)
  - Twyn -- Charles II, 1994-2000; cuid34508 (Box 143, Folder 23)
  - Stalin the Executioner -- Alberto Gonzales -- Marxism, 1996-2007; cuid34509 (Box 143, Folder 24)
  - Marxism in Universities -- Perfectly Maladjusted -- Psychotic Marketing, 1992-1996; cuid34510 (Box 143, Folder 25)
  - Paranoids -- Freudian Slip -- Too Generous -- All Alone, 1990-1991; cuid34511 (Box 143, Folder 26)
  - Afraid of Broadway, undated; cuid34512 (Box 143, Folder 27)
  - All the Doctors, undated; cuid34513 (Box 143, Folder 28)
  - Art: 2DS, undated; cuid34514 (Box 143, Folder 29)
  - Art Colony, 1990, undated; cuid34515 (Box 143, Folder 30)
  - Be Happy in Your Work, undated; cuid34516 (Box 143, Folder 31)
  - Beggars, 1995; cuid34517 (Box 143, Folder 32)
  - Bob [Dylan], undated; cuid34518 (Box 143, Folder 33)
  - Book of Perverbs, 1995; cuid34519 (Box 143, Folder 34)
  - Bribe, circa 2001; cuid34520 (Box 143, Folder 35)
  - Cambell's Kids, circa 1996-2010; cuid34521 (Box 143, Folder 36)
  - Casablanca, undated; cuid34522 (Box 143, Folder 37)
  - Cats, undated; cuid34523 (Box 143, Folder 38)
  - Chesterfields Mass Murder, 1998; cuid34524 (Box 143, Folder 39)
  - CIA Killers -- Why?, 1997; cuid34525 (Box 143, Folder 40)
  - Cig -- Dealing Drugs, 1998; cuid34526 (Box 143, Folder 41)
  - Cigar Aficianado, 1996; cuid34527 (Box 143, Folder 42)
  - Coney Mob, undated; cuid34528 (Box 143, Folder 43)
  - Crinoline, undated; cuid34529 (Box 143, Folder 44)
  - The Dishonorables, circa 2000-2010; cuid34530 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Dog Better than Man, circa 1997-2010; cuid34531 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Don't Make Trouble, undated; cuid34532 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Dreamland / Foolish House, 2000; cuid34533 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Economist on Anarchy, 2005; cuid34534 (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Einstein and Gravity, 2003; cuid34535 (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Elvis, undated; cuid34536 (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Elvis and Nixon, undated; cuid34537 (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Employed Artist / Writer / Actor, undated; cuid34538 (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Engineers for Glee, undated; cuid34539 (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Exit Art, circa 2004-2010; cuid34540 (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Feminists Against Censorship, 2002; cuid34541 (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Flying Saucers, 2000; cuid34542 (Box 144, Folder 13)
  - Food Series, 1987; cuid34543 (Box 144, Folder 14)
  - Forget?, 1993; cuid34544 (Box 144, Folder 15)
  - French Images, undated; cuid34545 (Box 144, Folder 16)
  - Friendly Strangers, undated; cuid34546 (Box 144, Folder 17)
  - From USPS Books, undated; cuid34547 (Box 144, Folder 18)
  - The Fucking Dead, undated; cuid34548 (Box 144, Folder 19)
  - Get that Communist, 2006; cuid34549 (Box 144, Folder 20)
  - Harvard International Review, 1993; cuid34550 (Box 144, Folder 21)
  - Holly and Mistletoe, undated; cuid34551 (Box 144, Folder 22)
  - Home Planet Cover, circa 1991; cuid34552 (Box 144, Folder 23)
  - I Pretend to Work, undated; cuid34553 (Box 144, Folder 24)
  - If the Rich Could Pay the Poor, 1995; cuid34554 (Box 144, Folder 25)
  - Illustrations to Use, undated; cuid34555 (Box 144, Folder 26)
  - Jingle Ass, 1997, undated; cuid34556 (Box 144, Folder 27)
  - Joe Camel Fucks Bailey's, 1991; cuid34557 (Box 144, Folder 28)
  - Johnny Cash, undated; cuid34558 (Box 144, Folder 29)
  - King Kong, undated; cuid34559 (Box 144, Folder 30)
  - Kittens, undated; cuid34560 (Box 144, Folder 31)
  - Labor Daze, 2005; cuid34561 (Box 144, Folder 32)
  - Love in Greenwich Village, circa 1995-2010; cuid34562 (Box 144, Folder 33)
  - Love Major, undated; cuid34563 (Box 144, Folder 34)
  - Luna Park, undated; cuid34564 (Box 144, Folder 35)
  - Marlene, undated; cuid34565 (Box 144, Folder 36)
  - Men Kill for What I Give, undated; cuid34566 (Box 144, Folder 37)
  - Millionaires, 1985; cuid34567 (Box 144, Folder 38)
  - Mixed Cartoons, undated; cuid34568 (Box 144, Folder 39)
  - Mixed Images, undated; cuid34569 (Box 144, Folder 40)
  - New Work, undated; cuid34570 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Noam and Chavez, 2003-2005; cuid34571 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Office Sinner, undated; cuid34572 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Only 21,000 Dead Canadians!, undated; cuid34573 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Over-Much Niceness, undated; cuid34574 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Peacemaker (Mini), undated; cuid34575 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Piggy Pears, undated; cuid34576 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Possible, 2002, undated; cuid34577 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Possibles -- Older, undated; cuid34578 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Puck, 1999-2000; cuid34579 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Revolution -- Festival, 2001, undated; cuid34580 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - RNC 2004, 2004, undated; cuid34581 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Salute to American Ingenuity, 2003, undated; cuid34582 (Box 145, Folder 13)
  - Shit Mines, undated; cuid34583 (Box 145, Folder 14)
  - Snarl, undated; cuid34584 (Box 145, Folder 15)
  - Splintered Commie, undated; cuid34585 (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - The State of the State, 2001; cuid34586 (Box 145, Folder 17)
  - A Stupid Bastard, undated; cuid34587 (Box 145, Folder 18)
  - To Do, undated; cuid34588 (Box 145, Folder 19)
  - Wall's Ice Cream, undated; cuid34589 (Box 145, Folder 20)
  - Warfare Time, 2003; cuid34590 (Box 145, Folder 21)
  - We Arm the World, 2001; cuid34591 (Box 145, Folder 22)
  - Welfare -- New Bill, 1996; cuid34592 (Box 145, Folder 23)
  - Wine Tits, circa 1995-2010; cuid34593 (Box 145, Folder 24)
  - Worst Book, undated; cuid34594 (Box 145, Folder 25)
  - Xmas, undated; cuid34595 (Box 145, Folder 26)
  - Xmas Cards, undated; cuid34596 (Box 145, Folder 27)
  - Cartoons, Collages -- Various, 2005, undated; cuid34602 (Box 145, Folder 28)
  - If Living was a Thing Money Could Buy, 1987-1988, 1995; cuid34603 (Box 145, Folder 29)
  - Mailing Packet of Cartoons for "FOR" and "JPF", circa 2006; cuid34604 (Box 145, Folder 30)
  - Jane Greer Gallery Show: Questionable Cartoons, 1987; cuid34605 (Box 145, Folder 31)
  - Cartoons and Collages -- Bribe, 1991-1992; cuid34598 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Cartoons -- Poster Sized, 1992-2001, undated; cuid34597 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Hymie the Hippie -- Original Art, circa 1988-2010; cuid34599 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1994, 2003, undated; cuid34600 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Karl Marx and Ethics of Capitalism, 1991-1993; cuid34606 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Great Moments in the History of Journalism, 1983-1994; cuid34607 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Cartoons/Collages, undated; cuid34608 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - New Cartoons -- Book of Perverbs, undated; cuid34609 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Recent Cartoons -- Great Moments in the History..., undated; cuid34610 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Ready to Mount -- Great Moments in the History of..., undated; cuid34611 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Labor 1 -- Do This Next -- Board This and Aphorisms, undated; cuid34612 (Box 148, Folder 7)
  - Labor 2, undated; cuid34613 (Box 148, Folder 8)
  - Teach Yourself Fucking -- Leftovers and Dups and Not Used, circa 1999-2000; cuid34614 (Box 148, Folder 9)
  - War Cartoons, 2002, undated; cuid34615 (Box 148, Folder 10)
  - Thelma Goes Berserk, undated; cuid34616 (Box 148, Folder 11)
  - Healing for Money, 2000; cuid34617 (Box 148, Folder 12)
  - Old Fucks at Home -- Help the Paranoids, undated; cuid34618 (Box 148, Folder 13)
  - More Marxists in Factories, undated; cuid34619 (Box 148, Folder 14)
  - Aids Cure, undated; cuid34620 (Box 148, Folder 15)
  - Karl's Pub Crawl, undated; cuid34621 (Box 148, Folder 16)
  - Stalin and Lenin's Commissars, undated; cuid34622 (Box 148, Folder 17)
  - Dr.: What Have I Got?, undated; cuid34623 (Box 148, Folder 18)
  - Woman Doctor, undated; cuid34624 (Box 148, Folder 19)
  - Circumcision, undated; cuid34625 (Box 148, Folder 20)
  - Dentist -- Sorry We're In, undated; cuid34626 (Box 148, Folder 21)
  - Alone, undated; cuid34627 (Box 148, Folder 22)
  - You're Too Generous, undated; cuid34628 (Box 148, Folder 23)
  - Freudian Slip, undated; cuid34629 (Box 148, Folder 24)
  - Private Prisons, 1995; cuid34630 (Box 148, Folder 25)
  - Police Chase / Hooray for Hollywood, 1981, 1995-1998; cuid34631 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Oklahoma -- Michigan Bomb, undated; cuid34632 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Perfectly Maladjusted, undated; cuid34633 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - High School Suicide, undated; cuid34634 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - What Good Are Kids?, undated; cuid34635 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - New Doctor, undated; cuid34636 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - American Medical, 1987; cuid34637 (Box 149, Folder 7)
  - Scalping Knives, undated; cuid34638 (Box 149, Folder 8)
  - Miss Education, 2002; cuid34639 (Box 149, Folder 9)
  - School Daze, 2000-2002; cuid34640 (Box 149, Folder 10)
  - Dying of Cancer, undated; cuid34641 (Box 149, Folder 11)
  - Docs: Savior -- Dogs, 1994; cuid34642 (Box 149, Folder 12)
  - Journalism Hist. / America, 1989-1992; cuid34643 (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Stray Bullets, Kids, 1998; cuid34644 (Box 149, Folder 14)
  - 6 Kills 6, 2000; cuid34645 (Box 149, Folder 15)
  - Tie a Scarf, undated; cuid34646 (Box 149, Folder 16)
  - Apartment Hunting Course, undated; cuid34647 (Box 149, Folder 17)
  - Cartoons (Layout Negative), undated; cuid34601 (Flat-file-folder 1)
  - Welcome Home -- Vietnam Vets!, undated; cuid34648 (Box 326, Folder 3)
- Series III. The Fugs, 1964-2008, undated; 12 Linear Feet in 10 manuscript boxes, 1 tall manuscript box, 2 hinged-ring binder boxes, 3 flat boxes, 6 oversize folders, 1 flat-file folder; 111 audiocassettes; 10 sound discs (vinyl); 4 sound discs (cd)
  This series has been arranged in alphabetical order by file title.
  This series contains setlists; announcements; clippings; sound recordings; photographs; and posters related to the band, The Fugs, who performed in various New York clubs during the 1960s and 1970s, including The Bridge, The Bowery Ballroom, and The Knitting Factory. Tour planning files, along with announcements and posters from the 1960s through the 2000s illustrate The Fugs' world-wide popularity. Audiocassettes, vinyl discs, and CDs contain recordings of the band's appearances and concerts, as well as interviews, local New York events, and their albums. Of note are recordings from the 1990 Fugs Orgy on WHRB in Cambridge, MA, and their 1994 Real Woodstock Festival concert. An audiocassette of a Bob Dylan radio interview from the 1960s in which he mentions The Fugs can also be found in this series. Scripts and recordings of songs related to a proposed Fugs-inspired movie project Fingers in the Sun, written by Kupferberg and fellow band member Ed Sanders can also be found in this series. See also Series VIII for Fug fan mail and Series VII for additional clippings and articles.
  - Advice from the Fugs, 2002 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Albany, 2000-2003 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Allen (Ginsberg) Memorial -- St. John the Divine, 1998 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Articles, Reviews, and Bios, 1966-2008 (Box 186, Folder 4-7, Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Beat Seminar / NoBar Cafe, circa 1993 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Beeber Book, 2008 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Bill Nevins Benefit at Bowery P.C., 2004 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Biographies, circa 1964-2010 (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - Bob Fass Show, 1999, undated (Box 186, Folder 12)